# Jeremy Li

www.jeremyli.space

jeremyli.0623@gmail.com

Tel: (781)-605-7163 39 Florence St, Boston, MA

## Objective

A software engineer also can get passionate on product. 3-year software engineering experiences not only bolster my technical capability but nurture product visions and business acumen. I have strong focus on product usability in the work and love to take actions on digging feature insights. I desire to launch captivated products that can help our customer be successful. Will learn whatever is needed to bring values on my team.

## Work Experiences

### Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA

#### Software Engineer, Developer Integration

Mar, 2018 - May, 2019

As being Engineer,

- Built friction-less third-party plugins/toolings to support user-friendly security customer community.
- Scaled Jira standalone server over AWS cloud-based ecosystem to reduce massive single point failures and refined technical requirements with team and achieved existing user's conversion rate from nothing to 21%.
- Worked on mitigating security risks by triaging security attacks and internal data compliance vulnerabilities. As being PM side role,
- Built up customer metrics via SumoLogic pipeline to track real-time API calling through the entire integration eco-system (7 product lines), facilitate Sr. management and partnership to make strategic decisions.
- Involved proactively in Agile Scrum and DevOps process (A/B testing, canary releases) to enable fully CI/CD pipeline, gained better product sense and SaaS enterprise insights.
- Gathered customer feedback (Webex/Email/On-site) and refined user persona for integration features.
- Collaborate with designers and engineers to be a liaison for cross-functional process and development.

### CA Technologies, Burlington, MA

## Software Engineer, Developer Integration

Nov, 2017 – Mar, 2018

• Implement and maintain a range of plugins/extensions of SaaS application security scan platform, led to increase at least 20% efficiency of proceeding application security scanning assessment.

#### Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA (Acquired by CA Technologies March, 2017)

## Associate Software Engineer, Core Platform

Jun, 2016 – Nov, 2017

- Tackled customer-faced technical problems and refactored the deprecated codebase.
- Launched visual studio extension into Microsoft Marketplace and got 6000+ downloads in 3 months.
- Been UX council member dedicated to my team, to unify and adopt best practice of front-end engineering.

## Philips of North America, New York

#### Software Research Intern, Acute Care Solution

Sep – Dec, 2014

• Processed, transformed large-scale healthcare dataset that can be later used for EMR research purposes.

#### **Technical Skills**

**Languages**: Java, JavaScript/ES6, C#, Python, HTML5/CSS(Sass/LESS)

Databases: MySQL, NoSQL Web Framework: React, D3.js, .NET Core, Bootstrap, Gradle, Gulp, REST DevOps: AWS, Azure, Jenkins, Docker

Spring MVC, Jupyter Notebook. Data Analysis

Other: Git, Jira/Confluence, Agile

Certification: PSM I (Professional Scrum Master), Google Analytics IQ

#### Education

### Northeastern University, College of Engineering, Boston, MA

M.S. in Information Systems

Sep. 2015

Related Course: Application Engineering, Web Development, Advanced Data Science, Organization Mgt.

#### Central South University, College of Engineering, Changsha, China

B.S. in Computational Material Engineering

Jun, 2013

Awards: 2nd prize in Challenge Cup Innovative Technology; "Most Influential Member", Engineer-Club. Leadership: College Vice-President of Innovation and Entrepreneurship Association.

## **Academic Projects**

#### U.S. Airlines On-Time Performance Analytics Project

• Cleaned, transformed large-scale datasets from RITA, visualized on-time performance as graphs and charts.

## **Healthcare Medical-Malpractice Informatics System**

Designed a national-wide model independently for adverse reporting of the healthcare system by Java.